let quiz=[
    {
      question: "The largest circular storm in our solar system is on the surfce of which of the following planets:",
      option: [
           "Jupiter",
           "Venus",
           "Uranus",
           "Earth",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "The biggest asteroid known is :",
      option: [
           "Vesta",
           "Icarus",
           "Ceres",
           "Eros",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Of the following four times, which one best represents the time it takes energy generated in the core of the sun to reach the surface of the sun and be radiated",
      option: [
           "Three minutes",
           "Thirty days",
           "One thousand years",
           "One million years",
      ],
       answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Rounded to the nearest day, the Mercurian year is equal to :",
      option: [
           "111 days",
           "88 days",
           "50 days",
           "25 days",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "One of the largest volcanos in our solar system-if not the largest-is named Olympus Mons. This volcano is located on :",
      option: [
           "Jupiter's Moon Callisto",
           "Venus",
           "Saturn's moon Titan",
           "Mars",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "One Jupiter day is equal to which of the following :",
      option: [
           "30 hrs 40 min",
           "9 hrs 50 min",
           "3 hrs 20 min",
           "52 hrs 10 min",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following best explains the shape of Milky Way Galaxy ?",
      option: [
           "Spherical",
           "Elliptical",
           "Spiral",
           "Barred-spiral",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The sunspot cycle is :",
      option: [
           "3 years",
           "11 years",
           "26 years",
           "49 years",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The andromeda galaxy is which of the following types of galaxies :",
      option: [
           "Elliptical",
           "Spiral",
           "Barred-spiral",
           "Irregular",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "About how many light years across is the Milky Way :",
      option: [
           "1,000",
           "10,000",
           "1,00,000",
           "10,00,000",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The Period from One full Moon to the next is",
      option: [
           "30.3 days",
           "30 days",
           "29.5 days",
           "28 days",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which Planet rains Diamond ?",
      option: [
           "Saturn",
           "Venus",
           "Neptune",
           "Jupiter",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following Planets has Greatest ecentricity ?",
      option: [
           "Pluto",
           "Jupiter",
           "Mars",
           "Mercury",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Heliocentric means around",
      option: [
           "Jupiter",
           "Moon",
           "Sun",
           "Neptune",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the Galaxy has Our SOLAR SYSTEM",
      option: [
           "Andromeda",
           "Milky Way",
           "Somberro",
           "Black Eye",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Largest Star in Our Solar System",
      option: [
          "Sun",
          "Polaris",
          "Sirius",
          "Vega",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    ]   
